---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We collect information from you when you register on our sites and gather data when you participate in the forum by reading, writing, and evaluating the content shared here.

When you visit our sites we use a third party service provider, Google, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the sites.

When registering on our sites, you may be asked to enter your name and contact information. You may also be asked to optionally provide additional information relating to your CAA operator or flyer information and membership details of other clubs. Your contact information may be verified. You may visit our sites without registering.

We also may retain server logs which include the IP address of every request to our servers.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To personalise your experience — your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
* To improve our club — we continually strive to improve our offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
* To send periodic emails — The email address you provide may be used to send you information, notifications that you request about changes to topics or in response to your user name, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
* To manage your Club membership.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We will:

* Retain server logs containing the IP address of all requests to this server no more than 5 years.
* Retain the IP addresses associated with registered users and their posts no more than 5 years.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Under Article 17 of the GDPR individuals have the right to have personal data erased. This is also known as the ‘right to be forgotten’.

To cancel your membership, delete your account and all of your personal data that we have stored, please visit the [Account Termination](https://greyarro.ws/tos#termination) section on our Terms of Service page.

-------------------------------------------------------------

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your device via your web browser (if you allow). These cookies enable our sites to recognise your browser and, if you have a registered account, associate it with your registered account and log you in automatically.

We use cookies to save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better experiences in the future.

We use cookies to provide both personalised and non-personalised advertising via a third party vendor, Google (Google Advertising Products).

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Google (in particular, Google Advertising Products) will have access to some data that we collect. This is to provide the personalisation of adverts and cookies and may be further used for personalised and non-personalised advertising. You can view Google’s Privacy and Terms policies at [https://policies.google.com/](https://policies.google.com/)

We do not sell, trade, exchange or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information (PII). We may release your PII information when we are legally bound to do so by the relevant authorities, or when we believe release is appropriate to protect ours or others rights.

--------------------------------------------------------------------

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our sites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

--------------------------------------------------

By using our sites you consent to this, our Privacy Policy.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Grey Arrows Drone Club Limited is registered as a data controller with Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) in accordance with Data Protection (Charges and Information) Regulations 2018 in England.

ICO Registration Number: ZB491575

A copy of our registration certificate is publicly available at [https://ico.org.uk/ESDWebPages/RegistrationCertificate/ZB491575](https://ico.org.uk/ESDWebPages/RegistrationCertificate/ZB491575)

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This document was last updated 2nd February 2023.

Powered by [Discourse](https://www.discourse.org/), best viewed with JavaScript enabled
